{
    "id": "6b807ffa97204fd8acdc7cbe77f8c3b4",
    "title": "Direct And Indirect Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sam asked me ........................ I was going to the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Rajiv said that he ......................... something to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needed",
                "needs",
                "was needing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Martin said that he ....................... that party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't like",
                "didn't like",
                "hasn't liked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Salini asked where ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was her bag",
                "her bag was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher told the boys ...................... quiet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to keeping",
                "keeping",
                "to keep"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Maria said that she ..................... to see the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "want",
                "wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Sophia said that she ...................... apply for that job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "had",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The policeman asked the woman where .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was she going",
                "she was going"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul asked me ...................... crying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why was I",
                "why I was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Suma told her mother that she .................. be working late that night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Manu asked his mother where ....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was his key",
                "his key was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother asked her son if he .................. his homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was finished",
                "has finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}